(Raj:)That's not him.
(Penny:)Oh, I can't wait for
you to meet everyone.
(Penny:)I told them all about you.
(Susan (Penny's mother):)Like what?
(Susan (Penny's mother):)Do they know about your brother?
(Penny:)Uh, not everything, just,
like, the jail and drugs part.
(Susan:)Why would you do that?
(Leonard:)What?
The world doesn't need
(Susan:)to know our problems.
(Penny:)Well, Mom, I'm sorry, but...
(Wyatt (Penny's father):)Hey, look, they got
Walgreens here, too.
(Susan:)You really think it's helpful
to change the subject, Wyatt?
(Wyatt:)Just trying to make this
a happy trip, dear.
Well, quit it!
(Penny:)So, uh, Randall,
can't believe
(Penny:)after all these years
you finally get to visit me
(Penny:)in California.
(Randall (Penny's brother):)Well, good thing I was
a nonviolent offender,
(Randall (Penny's brother):)otherwise I couldn't
have left the state.
(Penny:)All right,
that's enough jail talk.
Penny knows where I was;
she sent me cigarettes.
(Susan:)You sent
your brother cigarettes?
(Wyatt:)He was cooking and selling
crystal meth, Susan,
(Wyatt:)I think we can
let the cigarettes slide.